Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress
- Series I: Pacific Ocean
  - Group 13 - Pacific Ocean U.S. Navy Index, 17686411
    - 0810S (Folder Barcode: 00275670388)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0006 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0008 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province data. 0008 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province data. 0009 Color-coded tracks with soundings, contours, and province data. 0010 Tracks with select soundings and contours.
    - 0811S (Folder Barcode: 00275670376)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0002 Vema – 17, Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0005 Vema-17, soundings. 0006 Soundings collection sheet. 0007 Soundings. 0008 Vema-17, soundings and contours. 0009 Soundings and province map data. 0010 Vema-17, color-coded tracks with soundings and province data. 0011 Vema-17, profile.
    - 0812S (Folder Barcode: 00275682767)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Select soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0005 Preliminary province map. 0006 Color-coded track, soundings, and province map data. 0007 Profile, color-coded.
    - 0813S (Folder Barcode: 00275682779)
      0001 Soundings and province map data. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province map data. 0003 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0004 Vema-17, soundings. 0005 Select soundings. 0006 Select soundings. 0007 Soundings. 0008 Tracks. 0009 Select soundings. 0010 Vema-17, colored profile.
    - 0901N (Folder Barcode: 00275670364)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0006 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0007 Soundings. 0008 Tracks with soundings. 0009 Computer soundings. 0010 Tracks and contours. 0011 Tracks. 0012 Soundings.
    - 0902N (Folder Barcode: 00275670352, 00275670340)
      0001 Tracks and Scripps contours. 0002 Computer soundings. 0003 Tracks with soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0006 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0007 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province data. 0008 Contours and sea mount heights. 0009 Soundings. 0010 Composite Soundings. 0011 Contours with security notice. 0012 Final sounding compilation sheet, transparency.
    - 0902S (Folder Barcode: 00275670285)
      0001 Select soundings. 0002 Tracks with Soundings. 0003 Tracks with Soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Soundings. 0006 Soundings. 0007 Soundings. 0008 Tracks with Soundings. 0009 Color-coded tracks with Soundings. 0010 Color-coded tracks with Soundings. 0011 Color-coded tracks with Soundings. 0012 Computer plotted spot depths. 0013 Computer soundings.
    - 0903N (Folder Barcode: 00275670327)
      0001 Final soundings transparency for minerals assessment bathymetric chart.
    - 0903S (Folder Barcode: 00275670315)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0005 Select soundings. 0006 Computer soundings.
    - 0904S (Folder Barcode: 00275670303)
      0001 Tracks. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0005 Computer soundings.
    - 0905S (Folder Barcode: 00275670297)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks. 0003 Select soundings. 0004 Spot depths. 0005 Computer soundings. 0006 Spot depths.
    - 0906S (Folder Barcode: n/a)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0005 Color-coded tracks with soundings.
    - 0907S (Folder Barcode: 00275670273)
      0001 Tracks with soundings. 0002 Computer tracks. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings.
    - 0908S (Folder Barcode: 00275670261)
      0001 Select soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Select soundings. 0004 Select soundings.
    - 0908S and 0909S (Folder Barcode: 0027567025A)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings.
    - 0909S (Folder Barcode: 00275670248)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Tracks. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province data.
    - 0910S (Folder Barcode: 00275670236)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province data.
    - 0911S (Folder Barcode: 00275670224)
      0001 Select soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Worksheet. 0004 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province data.
    - 0912S (Folder Barcode: 00275670212)
      0001 Tracks. 0002 Select soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0005 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province data. 0006 Soundings with province data.
    - 0913S (Folder Barcode: 00275670200)
      0001 Tracks. 0002 Select soundings. 0003 Select soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province data. 0005 Color-coded tracks with soundings and province data.
    - 1001N (Folder Barcode: 00275670194)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with soundings.
    - 1001N (Folder Barcode: 00275670194)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0002 Historic soundings. 0003 Historic soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0005 Tracks with select soundings. 0006 Computer soundings. 0007 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0008 Soundings. 0009 Soundings. 0010 Province data. 0011 Computer plotted earthquakes.
    - 1002N (Folder Barcode: 00275670169)
      0001 Tracks. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Tracks with select soundings. 0004 Select soundings. 0005 Select soundings. 0006 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0007 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0008 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0009 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0010 Soundings. 0011 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0012 Soundings collection sheet. 0013 Bathymetric assessment chart – Dill project. 0014 Seamount chart. 0015 Mineral assessment bathymetric chart. 0016 Soundings from Long Lines Cruise 8. 0017 Computer soundings.
    - 1002N and 1003N (Folder Barcode: 00275670170)
      0001 Vema 32 soundings.
    - 1002S (Folder Barcode: 00275670157)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Computer soundings. 0006 Computer soundings.
    - 1003N (Folder Barcode: 00275670145, 00275670133)
      0001 Historic soundings with classification notation. 0002 Historic tracks and soundings with classification notation. 0003 Vema 32 – tracks and soundings. 0004 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0005 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0006 Soundings. 0007 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0008 Mineral assessment bathymetric chart. 0009 Mineral assessment bathymetric chart. 0010 Robert Conrad tracks with contours. 0011 Scripps contours. 0012 Contours. 0013 Computer plotted earthquakes.
    - 1003S (Folder Barcode: 00275670121)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Computer soundings.
    - 1004S (Folder Barcode: 00275670108)
      0001 Spot depths. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0004 Computer plotted soundings. 0005 Computer plotted soundings.
    - 1005S (Folder Barcode: 0027567011A)
      0001 Spot depths. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0006 Computer plotted soundings.
    - 1006S (Folder Barcode: 00275670091)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0004 Nazca Plate grid.
    - 1007S (Folder Barcode: 0027567008A)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with select soundings.
    - 1008S (Folder Barcode: 00275670078)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with select soundings.
    - 1009N (Folder Barcode: 00275670066)
    - 1009S (Folder Barcode: 00275670054)
      0001 Color-coded tracks with select soundings. 0002 Color-coded tracks with soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks with select soundings.
    - 1010S (Folder Barcode: 00275670042)
    - 1011S (Folder Barcode: 00275670030)
      0001 Color-coded track with select soundings.
    - 1012S (Folder Barcode: 00275670029)
    - 1013S (Folder Barcode: 00275670017)
      0001 Computer plotted soundings. 0002 Color-coded track with select soundings. 0003 Color-coded track with soundings and province data.
    - 1101N (Folder Barcode: 00275670005)
      0001 Tracks. 0002 Computer plotted soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Soundings. 0006 Soundings with corrections. 0007 Color-coded soundings. 0008 Color-coded soundings. 0009 Color-coded soundings. 0010 Soundings. 0011 Soundings. 0012 Computer plotted earthquakes. 0013 Select soundings.
    - 1102N (Folder Barcode: 00275673407, 00275673390, 00275673389)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Computer-plotted soundings. 0003 Color-coded tracks and soundings. 0004 Color-coded select soundings. 0005 Computer-plotted soundings. 0006 Soundings. 00067 Select soundings. 0008 Soundings. 0009 Color-coded soundings. 0010 Master soundings sheet. 0011 Color-coded master soundings sheet. 0012 Soundings and color-coded soundings. 0013 Soundings. 0014 Soundings. 0015 Select soundings. 0016 Select soundings. 0017 Select soundings. 0018 Sea mounts. 0019 Tracks and Scripps contours. 0020 Earthquakes. 0021 Soundings compilation sheet with Scripps picks for the mineral assessment bathymetric chart. 0022 Final soundings compilation sheet, for the mineral assessment bathymetric chart.
    - 1102S (Folder Barcode: 00275673377)
      0001 Computer-plotted soundings. 0002 Color-coded select soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Color-coded soundings. 0005 Soundings.
    - 1103N (Folder Barcode: 00275673353, 00275673365)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Vema soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Computer plotted soundings. 0005 Select soundings. 0006 Soundings. 0007 Color-coded soundings. 0008 Color-coded select soundings. 0009 Computer plotted soundings. 0010 Color-coded master soundings. 0011 Master soundings sheet. 0012 Color-coded master soundings sheet. 0013 Select soundings. 0014 Seamounts and contours. 0015 Contours. 0016 Seamounts. 0017 Scripps contours. 0018 Soundings compilations sheet for the Dill Project. 0019 Soundings compilations sheet for the Dill Project. 0020 Scripps profiler record picks. 0021 Dill project soundings compilation sheet.
    - 1103S (Folder Barcode: n/a)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Seamounts.
    - 1104N (Folder Barcode: 00275673341, 0027567333A, 00275673328)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Soundings and corrections. 0004 Color-coded soundings collection sheet. 0005 Master soundings collection sheet. 0006 Color-coded master soundings collection sheet. 0007 Master soundings collection sheet. 0008 Master soundings collection sheet. 0009 Corrections for master soundings collection sheet. 0010 Tracks and select soundings. 0011 Tracks and select soundings. 0012 Computer plotted soundings. 0013 Select soundings. 0014 Select soundings. 0015 Sea mounts. 0016 Contours. 0017 Scripps contours. 0018 Contours.
    - 1104S (Folder Barcode: 00275673316)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Computer plotted soundings. 0005 Sea mounts.
    - 1105N (Folder Barcode: 00275673304)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Select soundings.
    - 1105S (Folder Barcode: 00275673298)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings and corrections. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Color-coded soundings. 0005 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Computer plotted soundings.
    - 1106S (Folder Barcode: 00275673286)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Color-coded select soundings. 0003 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1107S (Folder Barcode: 00275673274)
      0001 Grid sheet. 0002 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1108S (Folder Barcode: 00275673262)
      0001 Grid sheet. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1109S (Folder Barcode: 00275673250)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings.
    - 1110S (Folder Barcode: 00275673249)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Select soundings.
    - 1111S (Folder Barcode: 00275673237)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1112S (Folder Barcode: 00275673225)
    - 1113S (Folder Barcode: 00275673213)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Select soundings.
    - 1201N (Folder Barcode: 00275673201)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Tracks with select soundings. 0005 Soundings. 0006 Soundings. 0007 Color-coded soundings with corrections.
    - 1202N (Folder Barcode: 00275673195)
      0001 Track locations and soundings. Note: “Tell this track making SOB to please be more careful in spotting his soundings.”-Foster. 0002 Select soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Select soundings. 0005 Color-coded soundings. 0006 Soundings with corrections. 0007 Soundings collection sheet. 0008 Collection sheet with corrections. 0009 Color-coded soundings. 0010 Soundings collection sheet. 0011 Tracks with select soundings. 0012 Soundings collection sheet with corrections. 0013 Soundings collection sheet for the Dill project. 0014 Mineral assessment bathymetric chart. 0015 Mineral assessment bathymetric chart with highlighted soundings. 0016 Computer plotted soundings. 0017 Contours. 0018 Province map. 0019 Color-coded contours. 0020 Scripps contours. 0021 Soundings compilation sheet negative transparency.
    - 1202S (Folder Barcode: 00275673183)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Soundings. 0006 Computer plotted soundings.
    - 1203N (Folder Barcode: 00275673171)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Color-coded soundings with corrections. 0005 Color-coded soundings collection sheet. 0006 Tracks with select soundings. 0006 Soundings collection sheet. 0008 Computer plotted soundings. 0009 Computer plotted soundings. 0010 Computer plotted soundings with corrections. 0011 Province map. 0011 Color-coded contours. 0013 Contours. 0014 Scripps contours. 0015 Soundings compilation sheet with averages. 0016 Soundings compilation sheet. 0017 Soundings compilation sheet.
    - 1203S (Folder Barcode: 0027567316A)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Computer-plotted soundings.
    - 1204N (Folder Barcode: 00275673031)
      0001 Contours. 0002 Color-coded contours. 0003 Color-coded contours. 0004 Soundings plotting sheet. 0005 Soundings collection sheet. 0006 Soundings collection sheet. 0007 Soundings collection sheet. 0008 Soundings collection sheet with corrections. 0009 Soundings collection sheet with Matthew’s zones. 0010 Dill project collection sheet. 0011 Soundings correction sheet. 0012 Select soundings. 0013 Soundings master sheet. 0014 Track and soundings sheet. 0015 Contour map. 0016 SIO Contour map. 0017 Scripps contours. 0018 Scripps contours. 0019 Contours and sea mounts. 0020 Contours. 0021 Negative print – Scripps contours. 0022 Contours.
    - 1204S (Folder Barcode: 0027567302A)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Color-coded soundings. 0005 Color-coded soundings. 0006 Computer plotted soundings. 0007 Soundings and province map.
    - 1205N (Folder Barcode: 00275673018)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Track and soundings transparency. 0004 Negative print – Scripps contours. 0005 Soundings collection sheet.
    - 1205S (Folder Barcode: 00275673006)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings with corrections. 0003 Soundings worksheet. 0004 Color-coded soundings. 0005 Color-coded soundings. 0006 Color-coded soundings. 0007 Computer plotted soundings.
    - 1206N (Folder Barcode: 00275672993)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Contours. 0005 Negative print – Scripps contours.
    - 1206S (Folder Barcode: 00275672981)
      0001 Color-coded select contours.
    - 1207S (Folder Barcode: 0027567297A)
      0001 Grid sheet. 0002 Color-coded select soundings. 0003 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1208S (Folder Barcode: 00275672968)
    - 1209S (Folder Barcode: 00275673158)
    - 1210S (Folder Barcode: 00275673146)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Select soundings. 0003 Select soundings.
    - 1211S (Folder Barcode: 00275673134)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1212S (Folder Barcode: 00275673122)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings and province data. 0003 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1213S (Folder Barcode: 00275673110)
    - 1301N (Folder Barcode: 00275673109)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Soundings with corrections. 0005 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1302N (Folder Barcode: 00275673080)
      0001 Tracks with soundings and geographic locations. Note: “place your god damn sdgs [soundings] more carefully” – Foster. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Color-coded soundings. 0006 Master soundings collection sheet with corrections. 0007 Soundings. 0008 Color-coded soundings. 0009 Soundings with Matthew’s zones. 0010 Soundings for mineral assessment bathymetric chart. 0011 Soundings with corrections. 0012 Soundings for bathymetric chart. 0013 Half degree depth averages. 0014 Computer-plotted soundings. 0015 Computer-plotted soundings. 0016 Contours. 0017 Soundings and contours. 0018 Earthquakes, magnetics, and fracture zones for the Dill project. 0019 Tracks with select soundings. 0020 Scripps contours.
    - 1302S (Folder Barcode: 00275673092)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Select soundings. 0004 Computer plotted soundings.
    - 1303N (Folder Barcode: 00275673079, 00275673067, 00275673055)
      0001 Cable data. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Soundings and select soundings. 0004 Soundings and select soundings. 0005 Soundings and select soundings. 0006 Select soundings. 0007 Soundings. 0008 Final soundings transparency. 0009 Final soundings transparency. 0010 Soundings transparency. 0011 Soundings. 0012 Soundings and select soundings. 0013 Soundings and select soundings. 0014 Soundings and select soundings. 0015 Select soundings. 0016 Computer plotted soundings. 0017 Computer plotted soundings. 0018 Computer plotted soundings. 0019 Computer plotted soundings. 0020 Geologic Map for the Dill project. 0021 Half-degree depth averages for mineral assessment map. 0022 Half-degree depth averages for mineral assessment map. 0023 Soundings and contours. 0024 Soundings and contours. 0025 Color-coded soundings and province data. 0026 Contours. 0027 Tracks and contours. 0028 G.S. Pioneer Soundings.
    - 1303S (Folder Barcode: 00275673043)
    - 1304N (Folder Barcode: 00275672956, 00275672944, 00275672944, 00275672932)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Soundings and seamount contours. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Color-coded select soundings. 0005 Collection sheet. 0006 Soundings sheet with corrections. 0007 Soundings sheet with status information. 0008 Soundings collection sheet. 0009 Soundings collection sheet. 0010 Soundings with corrections. 0011 Computer plotted soundings. 0012 Computer plotted soundings. 0013 Computer plotted soundings. 0014 Soundings, computer plotted soundings, and bottom contours for mineral assessment chart. 0015A Pencil overlay for contours. 0015B Tracing paper overlay. 0015C Soundings collection sheet. 0016 Heezen geology. 0017 Half-degree depth average for mineral assessment chart. 0018 Color-coded soundings and province map data. 0019 Contour pencil sketch. 0020 Contours. 0021 Color-coded contours with select soundings. 0022 SIO contour map without tracks. 0023 SIO contour map with tracks.
    - 1304S (Folder Barcode: 00275672920)
      0001 Color-coded contours. 0002 Select contours. 0003 Color-coded select contours.
    - 1305N (Folder Barcode: 00275672919)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded select contours. 0003 Soundings collection sheet transparency. 0004 AT&T cable route from California to Hawaii. 0005A Contour overlay. 0005B Color-coded soundings. 0006 Contour map.
    - 1305S (Folder Barcode: 00275672907)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings with corrections. 0003 Color-coded soundings. 0004 Color-coded soundings.
    - 1306N (Folder Barcode: 00275672890, 00275672889, 00275672877)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Collection sheet transparency. 0006 Select soundings transparency. 0007 Select soundings. 0008 Soundings collection sheet. 0009 Soundings collection sheet and color-coded soundings. 0010 Soundings collection sheet. 0011 Soundings. 0012 Soundings. 0013 Master soundings collection sheet. 0014 Contours. 0015 Contours. 0016 AT&T cable route California to Hawaii.
    - 1306S (Folder Barcode: 00275672865)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Color-coded select soundings. 0003 Color-coded select soundings. 0003 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1307N (Folder Barcode: 00275672853)
      0001 Tracks with classification notations. 0002 Select soundings transparency. 0003 Select soundings. 0004 Soundings transparency. 0005 Soundings transparency. 0006 Soundings. 0007 Soundings. 0008 Soundings. 0009 G.S. Pioneer Soundings. 0010 G.S. Pioneer Soundings.
    - 1307S (Folder Barcode: 00275672841)
    - 1308N (Folder Barcode: 0027567283A)
      0001 Select soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Soundings. 0005 Soundings. 0006 Soundings collection sheet.
    - 1308S (Folder Barcode: 00275672828)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings.
    - 1309N (Folder Barcode: 00275672816)
      0001 Soundings. 0002 Soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Soundings with classification notations. 0005 Soundings with classification notations. 0006 Soundings with classification notations. 0007 Soundings. 0008 Soundings collection sheet. 0009 Soundings collection sheet.
    - 1309S (Folder Barcode: 00275672804)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Color-coded select soundings.
    - 1310N (Folder Barcode: 00275672798)
      0001 Select soundings. 0002 Select soundings. 0003 Soundings. 0004 Soundings collection sheet. 0005 Soundings collection sheet. 0006 Color-coded soundings collection sheet. 0007 Color-coded soundings collection sheet.
    - 1310S (Folder Barcode: n/a)
    - 1311N and 1411N (Folder Barcode: 00275672774)
      0001 Soundings.
    - 1311S (Folder Barcode: 00275672762)
      0001 Color-coded soundings
    - 1312S (Folder Barcode: 00275672750)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings. 0002 Color-coded soundings.
    - 1313S (Folder Barcode: 00275672749, 00275672786)
      0001 Color-coded select soundings
    - 1401N (Folder Barcode: 00275672737)
      0001 Color-coded soundings. 0002 Soundings.
    - 1401S (Folder Barcode: 00275672725)
      0001 Color-coded soundings.
    - 1402N (Folder Barcode: 00275672713, 00275672701, 00275672695)